Thank you very much.
Then we are now live.
Yes.
Oh.
Slapstick?
Slapstick.
Yes.
Mmm-hmm.
Today, too, we're going to work together,
GO!
Thank you very much.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
For cheering me up.
Yes, you did.
Hi!
Good evening.
I'm Balikata for this week's shift.
It's Balikata!
But I think it's a big hit.
It's a big hit.
I feel like we want to do it too.
We want to do it.
Can I do it with you?
It's like, "It's a balicata.
Let's go. Let's go.I'm going. Ready.
It's balicata!
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
Oh, no, it's not like that.
I wonder.
Isn't that finally happening recently?
A few iridescent clouds have appeared.
Yes, that's right.
About a week ago, you know,
It was summer, but there were no clouds at all,
I was basking in the sun the whole time,
It was cold,
But lately it's starting to look more like summer.
Iridocumulus clouds have appeared,
It has been raining from time to time.
It is getting a little bit cooler these days,
How are you all doing?
How are you doing, Balikata?
It was like a dream, wasn't it?
I don't know if it was a dream.
In a real sense.
It was a dream, wasn't it?
I love it.I like it.
Speaking of dreams,
Me, this one was with my master,
I dreamed that I was beaten up by my master.
I don't mean like this.
Hey! Like, "Hey!
I was like, "Why is Master so angry with me?
I'm asking him, but he doesn't answer.
He was like, "Oh, well....
He's looking at me.
He didn't really mean it.
Like a knack.
He won't stop at all.
Hey, hey! I'm just saying.
I get it, I get it, I get it! I get it.
Dreams are mysterious, aren't they?
It is strange, isn't it?
I don't even know why my master is being violent to me,
I don't even know why he's being violent to me.
It's just a dream, right?
It is a dream.
A dream.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's why I said, "Yes,Yes, so I said,
Well, let's, you know, let's proceed with the recording.
Yes.
Let's move on to the recording.
So, the weekend is just around the corner.
Yes, it's going fast.
How's it going? How is it?
How is it?
How's it feel?
What's it like? Weekends, you know, it wasn't so bad when I was younger,
I'm sure there are a lot of working people who are watching this now,
After a week of work, on Fridays, I feel like I've done all I can do,
I felt like I had done my job,
You've done your job, right?
I feel like going out to eat or have a drink with everyone,
I want to go out to eat or have a drink with everyone.
Yes, I do.
Well, we do go out for drinks quite a bit.
Wow, I love it.
You love it.
I love it.
It's nice, isn't it?
How many weeks will you spend talking about my drunkenness?How many weeks are you going to spend talking about my drunkenness?
Come to think of it, you often talk about your surpon's father or mother on the show, don't you?
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
I finally saw them the other day.
Living things.
A living thing.
Live, live fubos.
It's a live fubo.
Raw fubo.
Well, they look alike.
I mean, they have the same face, the same atmosphere.
Yes, really?
A little soft and tender, but with a little bit of pressure, I guess.
Oh, yes.
Sarpong's father is! Dad said.
Dad said that. He said it. He said it as it was?
Yes, that's right. He said he was Sarpong's father.
Why?
Because he was so, you know, brisk.
I guess he was pretty much as I imagined him to be, huh?
Oh, really?
Dad.
That's great.Oh, that was good.
Oh, I knew it, I knew it.
That's great,
Thank you very much.
Where did you see me?
I had a one-man show.
You know, you live with your parents, don't you?
Yes, my parents' house.
After the concert, you met them at home again, right?
Yes, that's right. Yes, yes.
What did you talk about then?
No, but he picked me up in his car that day and drove me to the venue.
What?
My parents were having dinner somewhere, and they were waiting for me to finish.
And then we met up and went home together.
How close you are!
Always together!
What is that?
Really?
Really, really.
We go home together.
Yes, we do.
So, do you talk about anything in the office? About today's concert.
Basically, whenever there is an event like this in the Nakajima family, the parents start reflecting on the event.
What?Eh?
Your own performance.
Your own performance?
Oh, yes. I perform, don't I?
Oh, you surprised me.
Oh, that's right.
A performance of your father and mother.
Oh, no, no, no.
It was kind of like I was basically sitting there, but I was sitting there wondering if they were doing something.
Oh, I see.
Yes, well, they were saying how I should have done something about my performance, or that I did a good job.
A true reflection session.
Oh, that's right. We have a review meeting.
But on that day, to my great joy, I only received compliments.
Wow.
But when I said "no good" to him, he said "ah".
That's it.
Nakajima Prefecture. Everyone in Nakajima Prefecture is like this.
Yeah, that's right! Shut up!
It's like, "Shut up! But that day was pretty good.
I really don't want my parents, you know, to come and see the show.
If they do come, I definitely don't want them to come, but I would be happy if they came.
I would be happy if they came.
Have you ever seen Balikata's father and mother at EBITCHUNO?
Yes, I have. Familien, come to the Familien the other day, too.Yes, there is. Familien, you came to the Familien the other day.
Did he come?
And did he say anything afterwards?
Nothing?
Of course he did! Usually, he's like this, I dare you.
Really?
You don't say "I hate you" very often.
It's not wrong to say it.
It's not like I'm talking about something else.
Oh, I see.
Like, "Time break in Koshien is interesting.
It's really irrelevant.
Like, "It starts with Noah.
You guys talked like that, right?
No, I thought you guys were really close.
Well, well, well.
I understand. I mean, your father and mother were a little bit like that, right?
They seemed like friends.
Yes, that's right.
The atmosphere.
It's like my friend.
Dad, mom and dad!
Mother, father, mother!
It wasn't like that.It wasn't like.
Parents, oh sure.
It was something like, thanks! Like, "Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Hi! I'm Sarpong's father! Like that.
I didn't put him like a comic actor.
It wasn't like that.
I was really saying it.
No, no, no.
Yes, that's why.
Well, let's get on with it.
Let's go to this corner first, shall we?
Yes.
A riot of living creatures
Baraaan!
Yes, it's really him!
Oh, thank you very much, Mr. Shrimp Buddy, from Arakawa-ku, Tokyo.
Thank you very much for taking our picture together at the event at the barricade door.
I'm going to start looking for him.
We're going to start looking for him.
Good luck. I hope you find it.
This is the second time today. This week.
Why is this being sent to Pulp Fiction?
Of course it's still on the original server... but it's gone...
Scary!Oh, I'm scared.
Maybe this is...
Let's see...
Maybe this.
No, not this one.
Let's see...
Ah!
There it is!
The other day, I participated in a benefit event for Ebichu
to Yuna Nakamura of Barigatokoto.
Okera's pose
and took a two-shot with me!
It looks like this.
Is it that Okera?
That okera? The insect?
It's in the ground.
Yes, yes, yes.
Scrape it out of the dirt.
Have you ever seen an ocellar?
Maybe you haven't heard of it.
There's an insect called the okella.
They dig in the dirt like this, with their hands like shovels.
Why did he strike this pose?
I've always wondered about the pose of the okella.I used to do "Okera Pose" without knowing what it was.
I didn't know what it was.
That's because
It's a little bit questionable.
Don't feel like you're questioning it.
He told me...
"Okera is a cricket.
You can eat them.
I see.
And isn't that it?
Mr. Ebichu is planning to perform a new article called "Okera Disco" in October.
Mr. Ebichu is scheduled to perform a live show in October called "Okera Disco".
You've already commented on it.
Because it's Okera Disco.
It's this one.
Dancing Dip Review sent it to me.
Thank you very much.
I'll tell you the name of the creature.
Möwe!
Maeve!
I think I've heard that one before.
Möwe!
It's German, by the way.
Uh-oh.Uh...
I didn't know it was German.
Speaking of Möwe...
It's from Nausicaa of the Valley of the Wind.
So I've heard of it.
It's very famous.
I'd be a dahit if I told you.
It's in Nausicaa.
In Nausicaa?
Wow, I've never seen Nausicaa.
It's in the Valley of the Winds.
You should definitely see it.
I'm going to do it.
You should see it when you're young.
It's like you're still in puberty.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, let's see.
Cheat hat.
You all know what I'm talking about.
That's right... you all know stuff.
You're right.
You know what I think?
I think you should play Dibli.
Then there's nothing I don't already know.
That's for sure.Indeed.
Maeve.
Ah, master
German
Thank you.
It was German.
I wonder what it was...
It's in the movie "Nausicaa of the Valley of the Wind.
In Nausicaa of the Valley of the Wind.
It appears in "Nausicaa of the Valley of the Wind.
What was it?
It's quite popular among Ghibli fans.
It's a thing, isn't it?
Hey, hey...
Which one is it?
You mean it's down to two? That's what I'm saying.
Well, it's a living thing. Of course it is.
I mean, sure, sometimes they change it up, but would you rather have a living thing?
What? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's nothing.
Then I feel like I'm making a mistake. I feel like I'm making a mistake.
What always bothers me about my recordings is that I'm free time right now, so it's totally unrelated to the subject at hand.
You know, there are cameras with numbers 1, 2, 3, and 4, and number 2 and 4 are handwritten on a plate like a magic marker, right?
That's right.That's right.
There must be something else, something a little more proper. You know, something interesting. It's handwritten.
That's nice. Handwriting.
I wondered why.
That's funny.
Thank you.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's good.
I knew numbers 2 and 3 were funny.
It's so funny, isn't it?
And it's made with masking tape.
That's nice.
I can't use it.
It's fine.
You're working so fast these days.
Leave it to me.
You write fast.
Okay, first of all...
First of all...
Let's go pongon!
Here we go.
I've never seen anything like this.
The one that bites...
He bit Nabushka's hand.I'm gonna bite Nabushka's hand.
Wait a minute... that's a fox squirrel.
It's a fox squirrel.
Not even close.
But there are animals like this.
Of course there are.
They're a little fox-like.
Like a pig.
There are animals like this.
Maeve.
A little bit.
Scary, scary.
What the hell?
I thought it was called "Maevey".
I thought maybe it had lots of eyes.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's eyes, isn't it?
It's not hair.
There's something sticking out of it.
It's some kind of hair.
It's sticking up.
It's like it's angry.
So does the cat, when it goes "gah!
Yes, yes, yes.
Is that an eye?Is this an eye?
Scary.
Which one is real?
I don't know which version is the real one.
On the other hand, from a natural enemy's point of view...
I wonder if it's the natural enemy's way of looking at us.
Maybe it's like a painting.
Yes, sir.
So, Möbbe is...
A seagull.
It's a seagull. It's a seagull.
It's a seagull. "Mebbe" in German.
And the pronunciation... on the label... it's called "möbbey".
Möbbe... Möbbe...
Möbbey... that's right, that's it.
You know, in Nausicaä the Terrible, when Nausicaä is flying... that's Möbbe.
Is that Möbbe? It does look like a seagull, doesn't it?
It's from here, isn't it?
I see. Thank you very much.
Thank you for opening.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and... and...
And...
Hey, Dad...
Oh, that's it. Words of wisdom!Oh, that's just a word, isn't it? Words of wisdom!
Yee-ha ha!
This is... Yes!
I've got something cool to say. I got this from Mr. Chulman, the actor who supported us in Tokyo.
Mr. Keanu Reeves, the actor from "The Matrix"...
He looks just like Keanu Reeves.
He looks just like Keanu Reeves. I have a strong image of him from the Matrix, so I'm wearing sunglasses.
I remember when I was in the Matrix, I always used to do this when I was surprised.
Whenever I was surprised, I did this move from the Matrix.
I really miss it. It was in the mid 90's when I was playing the Matrix.
The images were shocking at the time, and now, for example, when you hit the screen with a bang, there's a bullet, you know, a bullet?
Nowadays, when you hit a bullet, you see a bullet.
It's a normal thing, but at that time, the Matrix was probably the first time in the world, I don't know, that bullets would come like this.
And you avoid the bullets like this, and then they hit you like this for real, for real, for real, for real.
It was really popular at the time, and the video was great.
Mr. Kianoliv said, "It's cool. A good sandwich is all you need in life.
Wow, seriously? Really?
Really? No, but Mr. Kianliv is famous for being a gentleman.
He's a cool guy.
By the way, is a sandwich enough for you?
Yes.
Yes, that's true.
I'd like to be that good. It's not easy.
I don't eat that much. What would you like?
I don't eat sandwiches that often.I mean, I'm sure there's buckwheat noodles and tonkotsu ramen, and I'm sure that's probably what I'd have had, too, if I'd been in Kia No Lives, but I don't know.
If I were Chianolivus, I'd have overribs and tonkotsu ramen and that'd be enough for life.
It's not cool. Maybe it's cool that I'm a sandwich.
Sandwich, that way. I'm not losing.
If the sandwich is a hundred percent, how's the tension?
How about we change it to something like this, like this, like this, like this, like this, like this?
Life is enough with empty space. Life is enough with good empty space.
I love those letters. I love those letters.
I love it so much.
I love it so much... because, you know, do they have letter spaces in Fukuoka? No, so I ate it for the first time when I came to Tokyo.
It was good, it was good, it was good.
I see...
Mojiyaki isn't so familiar to people on the west side of Tokyo.
That's true. It's pretty common in downtown.
I see. Moji is good. It's delicious.
By the way, you can eat salmon instead of sandwiches.
It has to be food, right?
A good crab cream croquette is enough for life.
What the heck... a sandwich is not good enough.
I think it's a little too fancy...
Sandwiches are great, aren't they?
I think foreigners love sandwiches.
Japanese sandwiches are like this, right? With ham and stuff, it's too much for them.
I heard it's very thick. I had one like this when I was abroad.
I've never been to a foreign country so many times.I've never been to a foreign country so many times.
I've never been to a foreign country so many times, but in Europe, there's a huge bread culture, and I know, Japan, or at least I don't eat that much bread in a day.
I don't understand why they serve so much bread.
And some kind of cornflakes with weird stuff in it, like milk in it.
It's full of dried blueberries... and dried fruit... it was good at first.
It's like a granola thing, like you eat it every morning.
And it's weird, I don't know how they do it, you know, with the egg on top of the cup like this.
I don't know how to do it... like in a hotel... there's some kind of egg stand...
Like this? You fry them, and when you drop them like this, the eggs fall out of the iron cup.
I didn't know that.
I was eating it like this, with the eggshell facing me like this.
Isn't it better to eat them like this? I heard it's more difficult than I thought...
By the way, I also received a quote from Eiko Koike, an actress, whom I'm sure you know.
Yes, I'm going out on a limb here.
It's not about whether we look alike or not, but I dare you to try to draw a portrait of me.
First of all, let me show you...
I'll show you...
No, no, no...
It's not that we don't look alike.
Why? I drew it carefully.
Why? It's all right. It has something to do with Koike-san's words of wisdom.
I'm sorry, Mr. Koike, but I really didn't mean to do it.
Eiko Koike's quote, sent to me by Miyamae Mask, aka Kawasaki Miyamae-kun.
I believe that opportunities will come to those who feel they are lacking something and are desperately seeking the next thing, rather than those who are passively waiting for it.
Well, taking that into consideration, I dare to write more than those who are passively waiting for something new.Well, I've taken that into consideration, and I'd rather write about it than just passively wait for someone else to do it.
Do you understand? What am I missing? I'm really not good at drawing women.
I'm really not good at drawing women.
I'm sure I'll get a chance if I keep at it. Thank you very much.
And...
Four photos from Serphone!
I sent a lot.
Airdrops.
Air-drop.
I got four pictures of the air-drop.
They're middle school airdrops.
Airdrops are awesome.
Yes, sir.
I can send four cards.
I don't know what to do.
Which one do we start with?
This one, this one, this one.
Oh, my God, this one.
This one.
Oh, my God!
Wow!
I'll go with that.
First of all...
Here you go.Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
I know you mentioned this earlier, but...
The one-man show...
I saw it.
Yes, I did.
Yes.
That's right.
Second one-man show.
Yes.
This time, we have a kind of theme title.
Art Workers.
Yes.
It's a little bit about art.
I had a one-man show.
Yeah, it was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun.
You looked like you had a great time.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's the best, isn't it?
That's true.
If the person doing it isn't having fun...
Yeah.Yeah. - Yeah.
It's definitely not fun to watch.
Oh, no.
All in all...
It was fun.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And...
A little further back in this hall
Yes, yes, yes.
And your father here...
Yes, yes.
Yes, there was.
Just below here?
Yes.
And after that...
Here.
Topmost.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
This one.
Ah! Unusual.
I launched it.
Yes, sir.
Oh!OH!!!
That 66 hardly ever launches.
Huh?
What? Why?
I don't know why.
It's not a hassle.
It's just... it's just...
Shingo and I...
Yes?
We're having a little launch party.
Yes.
We had it at an izakaya.
Nice!
Yes, it's great!
Why do you look so unhappy?
Ha-ha-ha!
There's a little food in there.
Oh, really?
Ha-ha-ha.
It's time to mooch!
Yes.
Oh, yes.
That was delicious.
It's good.That's nice.
Yes, sir.
And...
And let's go to the bottom.
The bottom.
Yes, sir.
Bray.
I went to the bathhouse recently.
Yes, yes.
I've been going around a lot.
Yes.
Among them...
There's a bathhouse in Takada...
Sekai-ryu
I've heard of it.
Yes, I have
Well...
I...
You like Kiss sauna, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Well...
I couldn't make it to the sauna that day.
I couldn't make it to the sauna.
I couldn't make it to the sauna, but...Yeah. - Yeah.
It's a very old-fashioned bathhouse.
It says something like...
It's got some kind of writing on it, like Mt.
Like Mt. Fuji.
Something like that.
It was written in a kind of mosaic art.
huh?
And what is it?
What is it?
A shower?
Yes.
It's not the kind that extends, but the kind that's already installed.
That's why it's here.
I see... I see...
It doesn't work.
You're the one that's supposed to be moving.
I'm the one...
I've got it. I've got it.
If you can't reach them, you have to move yourself.
I see.
In the shower at the bathhouse...
Yes, yes, yes.
I thought it was very elegant.
I see.Heh.
That's why I'm going to Kyoto.
I went there the other day.
I went to a lot of those types of bathhouses.
It makes me want to visit all the sento in the world.
It's so nice, isn't it?
I'm really into sento these days.
When I think of a public bathhouse...
What kind of chairs do you sit on?
They are always yellow
Yellow.
Like terratins.
Right.
Like yellow terratins.
Like yellow terratin
I can't get enough of those.
It's nice, isn't it?
I want one of those.
I know what you mean.
I want to sit on it at home.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And...
This one.This is it.
Just a minute.
Yes, this way.
I'd like to take Rasha out of the picture, which is a bit unusual.
Wow!
Is that pork back fat?
Yes, it is.
It's from the Hope Circle.
Wow!
Do you know it?
Of course I know it.
It's ramen.
It's the most famous of the Hope Circle, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
Moto.
Yuan, you mean?
Yes.
There's a famous restaurant in Tokyo?
That's right.
And this ramen
For me and my partner Shingo.
I have fond memories of this ramen.
Oh...
The Hope Circle?
That's right.Oh, yes.
We've been together since middle school.
From elementary school?
We work together.
Shingo and I have been working together.
Ever since then.
Whenever we had a job...
"Let's go to the Hope Circle after work.
You know...
And we've been doing that for about 13 years.
Wow!
We continued to eat there over time.
And then Shingo and I went to eat together.
And...
And that day was after the one-man rehearsal, so...
eh
And afterwards
Together
That's right... together.
I'd die if I ate this.
Really.
It's like some kind of overkill.
I'll eat it with a lot of blood oil.
Oh, my God.Oh, my God.
It's delicious.
The ramen at this restaurant
Mr. Vanicata has this kind of
I don't know...
You don't mind if it's a little bit strong?
Yes.
I've only had tonkotsu ramen.
Oh.
Well...
Maybe more than Tonkotsu.
Tonkotsu is better.
It's delicious.
Yeah.
But...
But...But...
It's probably a lot richer than Tonkotsu.
Yes, it is.
More than meat.
Muddy.
More like mud.
Yes.
Anyway...
It's all that pork back oil.
Yeah.
Heh...
The back oil is like this.
Yes.
Like that.
I used to go to Senkoya near the National Stadium.
I don't know if it's Senko-ya, but I used to go there.
Anyway... you know...
There was a counter, and when you went to the counter, there was oil on the counter, and it was like, "Oh, oh, oh!
It's like, "Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
The floor is very slippery.It's so greasy and slippery.
I don't need this any more...
This is what I came here to experience.
I really hope there will be an abundance zone in Yokohama.
Thank you very much for your time.
I'm sure you'd like to do it again, wouldn't you? I'm sure they'd like to.
Well then...
Let's do it with everyone, like that Friday Roadshow show "Balsu" with Nitel.
Let's do it with as many people as possible. I don't think there'll be any problems.
Okay, then...
Let's start with the first one.
We'll do it again next week, live at 7:00 p.m.
We'll see you next week.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.